In 28 days it began. In 28 weeks it spread. In 28 years it evolved.
28 Years Later is a horror, thriller, science
fiction film directed by Danny Boyle.
Twenty-eight years after the Rage virus outbreak,
Britain remains sealed off from the world.
A fortified island community survives in isolation—until a young boy’s journey to the
mainland reveals how both the infected and the survivors have evolved.
Isla, played by Jodie Comer.
Spike, played by Alfie Williams.
Jamie, played by Aaron Taylor-Johnson.
Dr. Ian Kelson, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Erik Sundqvist, played by Edvin Ryding.
Sam, played by Christopher Fulford.
28 Years Later is a 2025 post-apocalyptic coming-of-age horror-drama film
produced and directed by Danny Boyle and written by Alex Garland.
The third film in the 28 Days Later film series, it stars Jodie Comer, Aaron
Taylor-Johnson, Jack O'Connell, Alfie Williams, and Ralph Fiennes.
The film tells the story of a boy living in a post-apocalyptic world who undertakes a hazardous
journey with his ill mother in an effort to obtain medical treatment for her.
28 Years Later marks the returns of Boyle, Garland and
cinematographer Anthony Dod Mantle to the film series.
Cillian Murphy, who starred in the first film, served as executive producer.
The film was shot back-to-back with its sequel, 28 Years Later: The Bone Temple,
which was directed by Nia DaCosta and released in January 2026.
28 Years Later was released in the United Kingdom and the United States by Sony
Pictures Releasing through its Columbia Pictures label on 20 June 2025.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed
$151 million worldwide against a budget of $60 million.
The film explores themes of england, post-apocalyptic
future, satanism, satanist, sequel.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.